I don't move my fingers at all.
全然指を動かさないんだけど
Well, my abs are amazing.
あ んだけ腹筋すごいんだけど
Is it no good?
ダ メなの?
Walk a little closer and there's a table here.
少し近づいて、ここにテーブルがあって
Put your foot here, come in here and ride it.
ここに足を乗っけて、ここに入り乗っけて
Body like this, legs like this.
体をこうして、足を
Wow, it looks good.
すごい、よく見える
what up
どうした
Huh?
んだ?
middle
真 ん 中
Because I don't think I should do it.
やって いけないと思うからね
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
One neck, the muscles are different.
一首、筋骨が違う
Erase it below.
下に消して
Turn your back, butt to your left,
後ろ、お尻を向けて、左に向いて、
Turn to the right.
右に向いて
I'll crush your hand.
手をつぶしてあげるから
I'm shaking all the time.
ずっと震えてるよ
It's kind of bubbling, though.
なんか泡立ってきてるけど、
Something.
なんか
This is getting whiter.
こ っちの白されてきてるよ、これ
It's like I'm pulling the strings.
糸引いてるもんだって
Erotic.
エロ
It's messier than before,
さっきよりぐっちゃぐちゃじゃん、
this.
これ
Did it feel that good?
そんな気持ちよかった?
そんなに気持ちよかったの?
please.
お願いします
It felt so good, I got sick.
こっち気持ちよすぎてさ、病で立っちゃった
I was sick and had to stand up.
病で立っちゃったんだけどね、
this.
これ
Tighten up.
ぎ ゅーっとして
I want to keep it tight.
ぎゅーっとしておきたいのに
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
A little bit
ちょっとエ
B: That's too much.
ロ すぎるよね
It's so erotic that I'm already sick with this disease.
エロすぎて、もうこの病病なんだけど
We're both so shaken up.
ガクガクだもん、二人とも
My legs are shaking.
足がガクガクだもん
I haven't received a gear card yet.
まだギアカードいってないよ
picture?
え?
Gear card?
ギアカード?
Did I teach you how to take care of yourself?
お世話を教えましたっけ?
What about you all?
皆さんはどうですか?
How are you all doing?
皆さん は どう ですか?
That's all for this novel.
今回の小説はここまでです
I feel like I need to take care of you today.
今日は お 世 話 を し な けれ ばならないような
That's the feeling.
という 気 持 ちですね